Welcome to Blackwood. Where lost girls find their way.
Down a Dark Hall is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Rodrigo Cortés.
Kit, a troubled girl, is sent to the exclusive Blackwood boarding school, where she discovers that only four other female students have
been admitted to learn the four pillars of knowledge under the ominous wing of the mysterious headmistress Madame Duret.
Kit, played by AnnaSophia Robb.
Madame Duret, played by Uma Thurman.
Izzy, played by Isabelle Fuhrman.
Veronica, played by Victoria Moroles.
Jules, played by Noah Silver.
Ashley, played by Taylor Russell.
Down a Dark Hall is a 2018 supernatural horror film directed by Rodrigo
Cortés and written by Chris Sparling and Michael Goldbach.
It is based on the 1974 novel of the same name by Lois Duncan.
Summit Entertainment released it in select theaters and through
video-on-demand in the United States on August 17, 2018.
The film explores themes of boarding school, music teacher,
haunted house, private school, possessed.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.